<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Jelili O. Adesina</title><link>https://jelilio.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Jelili O. Adesina</description><image><title>Jelili O. Adesina</title><url>https://jelilio.github.io/images/papermod-cover.png</url><link>https://jelilio.github.io/images/papermod-cover.png</link></image><generator>Hugo -- 0.119.0</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 18:19:24 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jelilio.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Internationalisation in Java</title><link>https://jelilio.github.io/posts/i18n-in-java/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2024 18:19:24 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://jelilio.github.io/posts/i18n-in-java/</guid><description>Overview Internationalisation (i18n) refers to designing and preparing software to be easily adapted to various languages, regions, and cultures without requiring engineering changes to the code. This is usually followed by localisation (l10n), which involves adapting the internationalised software to a specific locale, including translating the text, adjusting for local conventions, and modifying other locale-specific elements.
The goal is to make the software flexible enough to support multiple locales by separating the core logic from locale-specific elements like language and cultural conventions.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://jelilio.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jelilio.github.io/about/</guid><description>Jelili is a dedicated full-stack software engineer with over eight years of experience in software development. Currently, he works as a Freelancer, specialising in developing scalable and efficient software solutions for clients across various industries.
Before being a Freelancer, Jelili worked at ActivEdge Technologies, where he used his backend development and database management skills to lead a team of backend engineers in developing world-class solutions.
Jelili holds a Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Computing Science from Griffith College, where he graduated with honours.</description></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>https://jelilio.github.io/projects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://jelilio.github.io/projects/</guid><description> Smart Home Security System with Raspberry Pi and OpenCV A Simple Blog with Express and MongoDB A Spring Application using Jenkins for CI/CD JWT Authentication and Authorization with OTP using Spring WebFlux JWT Authentication and Authorization with OTP using Quarkus A Single-page Application with Express and AngularJs An Online Code Editor using React Compiler API: exposes Websocket channel to accept source code and return the compiled output</description></item></channel></rss>